Every bellend online
is trying to teach you how to get rich.
But instead,
I'm going to teach you as a personal
trainer how I would make your
first $350 a day. This could get spicy.
And I've said this before, I say it again,
you must master in-person first, and
that goes to other niches too,
whether you're a physiotherapist,
whether you're a
psychologist,
whether you're a personal trainer.
So many people today arrive at the online
scene and go, "I want to work online."
And sell what, brother? What is it
that you think you're selling
if you have zero
experience doing the thing
that you want to sell?
Just because you went to the gym
and benched 100 kg does not make you a
personal
trainer. Now,
I can't say this enough either.
The sessions that you do in person
are some of the least paid sessions
possible.
But in years to come,
you're going to look back at them,
and they are going to be
the accelerators
that allow you to earn crazy amounts of
money.
And out of all the people
that you know that do the same job as you,
you'll earn
the most, and it's because of that.
We look at Adam Sullivan, EBT,
spent 10 years on the gym floor.
Even Joe Wicks got his reps in before
going online.
Kayla Itsines worked in a gym before she
became online.
I did three years,
5,000 hours of one-to-one sessions before
I went
online. And you need
that raw experience for every component of
being a great
online trainer.
So I'm going to say this again.
If you want to be great online,
you need to be great in person first.